BAINOMUGISHA LIBRA

librabainomugisha@gmail.com

+256-778764631 / +256 708523529

Bugolobi, Nakawa, Kampala.

01st/November/ 2023

To Human Resource Officer.

Microhaem Scientifics and Medical Supplies Ltd

P.O Box 73496 Kampala-Uganda

Dear Sir/Madam,

RE: <u>APPLICATION FOR QSSU-MHS-QA-QUALITY ASSURANCE SPECIALIST</u> (MEDICAL DEVICES MANUFACTURING) JOB AT YOUR ORGANIZATION.

I am writing to express my interest on the job position mentioned above. I am a female Ugandan with a Bachelor's Degree of Oil and Gas Management from Uganda Technology and Management University.

I have skills in computer, team work, and very flexible working in any environment. I pay great attention to detail and passionate on growing my career. Given an opportunity to work with you, I am prepared to use my skills and knowledge to contribute positively to growth of your Company.

I am looking forward to having an opportunity to discussing with you further on my abilities and nature of work.

Yours Sincerely,

libra

BAINOMUGISHA LIBRA

CURRICURUM VITAE

BIO DATA

NAME: BAINOMUGISHA LIBRA

DATE OF BIRTH: 09TH/JUNE/1998

GENDER: FEMALE

RELIGION: ANGLICAN

NATIONALITY: UGANDAN

EMAIL: <u>librabainomugisha@gmail.com</u>

CONTACTS: 0778764631, 0708523529

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Bainomugisha is a motivated and self-driven individual with good academic and interpersonal skills and the capacity to communicate clearly and simply with clients and colleagues while maintaining a high standard of honesty. She holds a Bachelor's degree in Oil and Gas Management from Uganda Technology and Management University and possesses extensive experience in the field of computing. Bainomugisha takes pride in being a member of a productive and successful team and has proven to have a good aptitude for leadership in a challenging and intensely competitive industry. Finally, Bainomugisha appreciates working in a team to solve challenges from the actual world and doing so with less oversight.

OBJECTIVE

I am currently seeking a new challenge that will put my professional skills to use for the good of the academia, the industry, the society as well as enhancing my career.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

Period	Institution	Qualification	
2019-2022	Uganda Technology and	Bachelor's Degree of Oil and	
	Management University	Gas Management	
2017-2018	St. Mary's College	Uganda Advanced Certificate	
	Rushoroza	of Education (UACE)	
2013-2016	St. Mary's College	Uganda Certificate of	
	Rushoroza	Education (UCE)	

OTHER TRAININGS AND COMPETITIONS

Period	Training	Organizers
January, 2023 – February, 2023	Digital Marketing	InfoClan Uganda Limited

WORK EXPERIENCE

PERIOD: September 2022 – September 2023

ROLE: Front Desk Officer/ Intern

ORGANIZATION: Uganda Technology and Management University

KEY ACTIVITIES: which include;

- Being an interface between the university and public by providing information for students and general public
- Being a liaison between the students and lecturers
- Answering to students day to day queries
- Managing all matters pertaining to reception/office appearance and utilities
- Issuing application forms and other relevant documents to prospective students
- Printing, photocopying and scanning of documents
- Preparing and serving tea to lecturers

PERIOD: May 2022 – July 2022

ROLE: Intern

ORGANIZATION: Ministry Of Lands Housing and Urban Development (MLHUD)

KEY ACTIVITIES: which include;

- Report writing and editing for meetings
- Planning and budgeting for physical planners and fellow interns as per intern supervisors guidelines
- Data collection with the use of GIS and analysis
- Team building with fellow interns and staff

PERIOD: May 2021 – August 2021

ROLE: Intern

ORGANIZATION: NILE ENERGY LIMITED (GAZ)

KEY ACTIVITIES: which include;

- Recording financial transactions and keeping the records for future use
- Offloading petroleum liquids
- Receiving and counting money collected from fuel pump attendants and banking assigned by the supervisor

SKILLS

- Graphics and design with use of Adobe Photoshop, illustrator and Canvas
- Computer literacy skills including Microsoft office packages (word, Excel, Access. PowerPoint)
- Computer management skills including troubleshooting hardware and software problems as well as operating systems
- Data entry
- Record management
- Communication both efficient and effectively
- Planning

INTERESTS

- Work:
 - Exhibiting confidence and responsibility at work
 - Team work and coordination
 - o Working under minimal supervision
- Leisure time:
 - o Prayers
 - Listening to music
 - o Adventuring

LANGUAGES

Language	Speaking	Writing	Reading
English	Good	Very good	Very good
Runyankole	Very good	Good	Good
Luganda	Good	Good	Good

REFERENCES

Dr. J.M. Okwadi Tukei, Ph.D

HOD Monitoring, Evaluation & Project Planning / Academic Staff Representative Council

Uganda Technology and Management University

Phone:+256 772 825 410

Email: tukeiokwadi@yahoo.co.uk

Miss.Nantongo Josephine

Centre for Transformative Parenting

Accountant

Phone:+256 779 990291

Email:nantongogeoze002@gmail.com

Mr.Mutaka Swaibu

Physical planner

Ministry of Lands Housing and Urban Development

Phone: +256-771 495625

Email: swaibu25@gmail.com